Resume

Hangchen(Daniel) Wu

Software & Web Developer

4 William St - Murrumbeena - VIC, 3163

T 0451018880 / wuhangchen2279@gmail.com / https://wuhangchen2279.github.io

A software & web developer who is proficient with a wide range of programming languages and development tools. Have a strong desire to learn more cutting edge technologies. Experience in all 5 stages of system development lifecycle including: requirement gathering, design, coding, testing, deployment, and maintainance.

EXPERIENCE

Nov 2015 -Current SPS COMMERCE

Burwood East, VIC

SOLUTION DEVELOPER

- Work on a translation engine to translate other message type (i.e. XML, CSV, SAP Idoc, etc) into EDI(Electronic Data Interchange) format.
- Maintain existing solutions and handle supporting query as needed.

Accomplishments:

- Familiar with technology stack: C#, XML, XSLT, .NET Core, SQL, GitHub, JIRA, Salesforce, Visual Studio, Windows Server, Jenkins.
- Awarded for Outstanding Performance in 2016.
- All projects delivered before due date.
- Work closely with team members to standardize team process.

Dec 2013 -Nov 2015

FINANCIAL MANAGEMENT GROUP

Melbourne CBD, VIC

JAVA WEB DEVELOPER

- Develop and maintain a website Business Coach Model.
- Update financial data on this website, and throubleshoot any errors if required.

Accomplishments:

- Familiar with technology stack: Java, Spring MVC, Hibernate, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, MySQL, TortoiseSVN, Eclipse, Linux.
- Upgrade back-end server to allow website run on a faster and stable platform.
- Quick turnaround time for bug fix.

EDUCATION

2012-2014

MONASH UNIVERSITY

MASTER OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

GPA: 3.188

Scholarship: International Merit Scholarship

2008-2012

UNIVERSITY OF TASMANIA

MASTER OF INFORMATION SYSTEM

GPA: 3.05

Resume

TECHNICAL SKILLS

C# & .NET Core & MVC	★★★★ ☆	XML & XSLT	★★★★ ☆
Java & Spring & Hibernate	★★★★☆	MS SQL & MySQL	***
HTML & CSS & JavaScript	★★★★☆	Git & GitHub & SVN	****
Windows & Linux & Mac	★★★★☆	Visual Studio & Eclipse	****
jQuery & Angular	★★★☆☆	Jenkins	***

SOFT SKILLS

Fast Learner	 Demonstrated by my past experience, I am able to get familiar with my job duty in around a month. Good at searching useful learning resources online (google, Github, stackoverflow) to enhance my knowledge.
Team Player	 Approable whenever team member have a question for me. Happy to share my ideas and suggestions in the team meeting. Contribute to team process optimization.
Time Management	Demonstrated ability to prioritize projects properly, and deliver them before due date.
Can-do Attitude	A strong willingness to accept and meet challenges.
Problem Solver	 Always quick turnaround time for production issue. Familiar with various debugging and testing tool.
Communication	 Demonstrated communication skills with good style of presentation. IELTS test result(0 - 9): Reading 8, Listening 8, Writing 7, Speaking 7

SIDE PROJECT

News Agency Website	 ASP.NET website to display information for News Agency Code: https://github.com/wuhangchen2279/GoodNewsProj Documentation: https://wuhangchen2279.github.io/news_doc.pdf
Airport Reservation	A .NET software used to book flight ticket
System	Code: https://github.com/wuhangchen2279/AirportPro
	Documentation:
	https://wuhangchen2279.github.io/wpf_airline_reservation.pdf
Mobile Health	Implementation of a personalized Mobile Health Monitor Android App
Monitor	Code: https://github.com/wuhangchen2279/MobileHealthMonitor
	Documentation : https://wuhangchen2279.github.io/android_doc.pdf
Book/DVD Search	Java website (iCompare) to search books and DVDs
Engine	Code: https://github.com/wuhangchen2279/iComparePro
	Documentation: https://wuhangchen2279.github.io/icompare_doc.pdf